pose.com 2014-07-01

# Privacy | Pose

  * How It Works
  * Shipping
  * Contact Us
  * FAQs

Effective Date: June 12, 2014

Pose Marketplace, Inc. (“Pose, “we” “us”) has developed this Privacy Policy which details important information regarding the use and disclosure of user information collected on the Pose’s websites that link to this Privacy Policy as well as our other related mobile applications, services, tools, and other applications that link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the "Site"). Pose provides this Privacy Policy to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using the services accessed through its Site (“Services”).

## Privacy Policy Highlights

### Personal Information Collected

When you use our services or make a purchase, you voluntarily share certain personal information with us (e.g., your name, e-mail address, address, mobile number, and/or credit card information).

### Access and Review Options

You can change your information at any time by editing your profile or account settings. You can also ask us for additional information we may have about your account at [support@pose.com](mailto:support@pose.com). We may retain certain information for archival purposes and if required by law.

### Tracking Technologies (Cookies, etc.)

We use tracking technologies such as cookies and other similar technologies to measure usage and provide information that will be of most interest to you.

### Your Information Choices

You can control how and when you want to receive promotional and certain system notifications from Pose. Go to your account settings to control these notifications.

### Uses and Retention

To operate our Site and contact you and third parties at your request. You agree that we can use the information as long as you have an account for the time and reasons outlined in this Privacy Policy.

### Updates to this Privacy Policy

You agree that we may notify you about material changes to this Privacy Policy by posting a new “Effective Date” on the Site.

### Disclosure of Information

By using the site you agree that we may share your personal information and other information we collect with our affiliated companies, our service providers, legal and law enforcement, others if there is a change of control and mobile carriers.

### Contact

Questions about our Privacy Policy or about our handling of your information may be sent to [support@pose.com](mailto:support@pose.com) or as otherwise set forth in the Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Terms of Service found at <https://pose.com/terms> (“Terms”). Each time that you access or use Sites, you signify that you agree to be bound by the Terms and this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the Terms and the terms of this Privacy Policy, you must discontinue accessing the Services available through the Site.

## I. INFORMATION WE COLLECT

**Registration, Product and Account Information.** You can browse the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information (i.e., name, email address, phone number, mobile telephone number, credit card information or physical contact information) about yourself. When you make a purchase or otherwise engage with Site you may provide certain non-public information. You may also provide payment information (e.g., credit or debit card information, name and billing address) to make a purchase.

**Information to respond to your requests.** You may give us your personal information so we can send you communications you request. Details of how you can opt-out of receiving any promotional communications from us are detailed in the section headed Accessing Your Personal Information.

**Sweepstakes And Other Promotions.** From time-to-time we may conduct contests or sweepstakes and may request information from you in order to enter. Participation in these contests or sweepstakes is completely voluntary. Contact information may be used to notify the winners and award prizes and file winners’ information and as required by law.

**Information Collected Through Tracking Technologies.** In addition to any personal information or other information that you choose to submit to us, we and our business partners may use a variety of tracking technologies that automatically (or passively) collect certain information from your computer, mobile, or other access device whenever you visit or interact with the Site (“Usage Information”). We use tracking technologies (including cookies, web beacons/GIFs, embedded scripts, e-tags/cache browers/web logs) to collect usage information. We may use tracking technologies for a variety of purposes, including:

  * Operationally Necessary. We may use tracking technologies required for system administration, to prevent fraudulent activity, improve security or allow you to revisit the site
  * Performance-Related. We may use cookies or other tracking technologies to assess the performance of our Services, including as part of our analytic practices to improve the content offered through the Services.
  * Functionality-Related. We may use tracking technologies to tell us, for example, whether you have visited the Site before or if you are a new visitor and to help us identify the features in which you may have the greatest interest.

Keep in mind that certain features of our Services are only available through the use of tracking technologies.

You may encounter tracking technologies/cookies from our third party service providers, that we have allowed on our Site that assist us with various aspects of our web site operations and services, such as [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/). If you want more information about these third parties click here.

We may also collect password information from you when you log in, as well as computer and/or connection information. During some visits we or our affiliated third parties may use software tools to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, time spent on certain pages and page interaction information.

Our goal is to collect and use only that information that we think is required for our legitimate business interests, in order to better understand your interests and improve your experience of using the Site.

**Information From Other Sources.** The information we collect may be combined with information from outside records (e.g., demographic information, navigation information, additional contact information) that we have acquired in accordance with the law.

**Contacting Us.** When you provide us with information in connection with a particular activity or otherwise sign up for our Services or provide your contact information, including an email address or telephone number in connection with that activity, product or service, you agree that this action constitutes a purchase or inquiry establishing a business relationship with us. You expressly consent to our communicating with you future information about our Services using the information you provided to us. You also attest that you have the legal authority over any telephone number you provide to us and can provide us with the authorization to contact you. This means we may contact you, in person or by recorded message, by e-mail, telephone and/or mobile telephone number (including use of automated dialing equipment), text (SMS) message, or any other means of communication that your wireless or other telecommunications device may be capable of receiving.

## II. HOW WE USE AND SHARE YOUR INFORMATION

**Use of Information by Us.** We may use Information that we collect about you: (1) to respond to your requests (2) provide customer service (e.g., to fulfill product orders made by you, to resolve disputes, problems with your account/profile or the Site or administer a sweepstakes or promotion (3) to improve our Services and to customize your experience; (4) to give you information about your account or our Services; (5) for internal business purposes; and (6) for purposes disclosed at the time you provide your information or as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**Analyze and Aggregate Non-Personal Information.**

We use aggregate information about our users and non-personal information to analyze the Site and user behavior and prepare aggregated reports which we may share with third parties.

**Communicate With You and Third Parties at Your Request.** We use your information to contact you to maintain your account, to comply with your stated communication preferences and to provide other Services requested by you, as described at the time when we collect the information from you, or to contact you for other purposes authorized by law.

**Mobile Data.** When you access the Site on a mobile device, we may use the information collected for any purpose set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**Offers and Promotional Messages.** We may also use your email address or mobile phone number to send you updates and communications about our products and services or other messages, such as newsletters, changes to features of the Service, or special offers. If you do not want to receive such messages, you may opt out or change your preferences by emailing us at [support@pose.com](mailto:support@pose.com) or contacting customer service at [310-452-4400](tel:310-452-4400). You also will be given the opportunity, in any promotional email or text message that we send to you to opt out of receiving such messages in the future by simply clicking “unsubscribe”. It may take up to 10 days for us to process an opt-out request.

**Legal Matters; Safety.** We may, without your consent, access and disclose your information, any communications sent or received by you, and any other information that we may have about you or your account as may be permitted or required by law (including, but not limited to, court order or subpoena), or to prevent or investigate suspected fraud, violations of our, or activity that appears to us to be illegal or may expose us to legal liability. Additionally, we may disclose your information in situations that we believe may involve potential threats to the physical safety of any person or property if we believe that your information in any way relates to that threat.

**Sale or Transfer of Business or Assets.** If Pose is sold or disposed of as a going concern, whether by merger, sale of assets or otherwise, or in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership, personal information of our users may be one of the assets sold or merged in connection with that transaction. Information about our users may also need to be disclosed in connection with a commercial transaction where we or any one of our businesses are seeking financing, investment, and support or funding.

## III. ACCESSING AND CHANGING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Users can review and change personal information, cancel the Service and close your autoship Service at any time by emailing us at [support@pose.com](mailto:support@pose.com) or contacting customer service at [310-452-4400](tel:310-452-4400). We may retain some information from closed accounts so that we can comply with law, prevent fraud, assist with investigations, resolve disputes, analyze or troubleshoot programs, enforce our Terms, or take other actions permitted by law. Likewise if your account is terminated or suspended, we may maintain some information to prevent re-registration.

## IV. CHOICE AND OPT OUT

**Opting Out of Promotional Messages.** You may choose not to receive our promotional communications or you may opt out of our sharing information with third parties for marketing purposes by at any time by emailing us at [support@pose.com](mailto:support@pose.com), going to our notifications unsubscribe page on pose.com or writing to us at “Privacy” Pose, Inc., 1009 Abbot Kinney Blvd, 2nd Floor, Venice, CA 90291.

**Administrative Messages.** As long as you have an active account, you may not opt-out of administrative e-mails (for example e-mails about your transactions or policy changes).

## V. IMPORTANT DISCLOSURES, PRACTICES AND CONTACT INFORMATION

**Links To Other Sites.** To the extent hyperlinks may be utilized to access external or third party sites, you should be aware that these external or third party sites are not controlled by us and, therefore, are not subject to this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you check the privacy policies of these sites to determine how your personal information will be utilized by the proprietors of those third party sites.

**Security.** We implement security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control. However, despite our efforts, no system can completely guarantee that there will never be unauthorized access to your personal information, and your use of Sites indicates that you are willing to assume this risk.

**A Note to International Users.** The Site is hosted in the United States. If you are using the Site from outside the United States, by providing your information on Site, you are consenting to the transfer of your information to the United States for processing and maintenance in accordance with this Privacy Policy and our Terms. You are also consenting to the application of United States law in all matters concerning the Site and Services.

**Children’s Privacy.** The Site is directed to a general audience and we restrict the use of our Service to individuals age 18 and above.

**No Rights of Third Parties.** This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to users of the Site.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy.** We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. You agree that we may notify you about material changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a notice on the Site. The most recent version of the Privacy Policy will always be posted on the Site, with the “Effective Date” posted at the top of the Policy. You should check the Site frequently for updates. By accessing the Site after the Effective Date you are deemed to consent to our then-current privacy policy.

**Your California Privacy Rights.** California Civil Code Section 1798.83, known as the "Shine The Light" law, permits our customers who are California residents to request and obtain from us a list of what personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year and the names and addresses of those third parties. Requests may be made only once a year and are free of charge. To make such a request, please contact us at [support@pose.com](mailto:support@pose.com). For all requests, you must put the statement "Your California Privacy Rights" in the body of your request, as well as your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. In the body of your request, please provide enough information for us to determine if this applies to you. You need to attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for our response. Please note that we will not accept requests via the telephone, mail, or by facsimile, and we are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or that do not have complete information.

**Contacting Us.**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy email us at [support@pose.com](mailto:support@pose.com) or contact customer service at [310-452-4400](tel:310-452-4400). or write to us at:

Pose Marketplace, Inc.   
1009 Abbot Kinney Blvd.   
2nd floor   
Venice, CA 90291 

**Third Parties Providers of Analytics Tools** This is a list of third parties we have hired to provide us information, reports and analysis about the usage and browsing patters of users of the Site.

**Cookies.** A cookie is a data file placed on a device when it is used to visit the Site. We use cookies to collect information for record keeping purposes, to make it easier to navigate the Site. Cookies are stored on users’ hard drives. We use both “session ID cookies” and “persistent cookies.” Session ID cookies are used to store information while a user is logged into the Site and expire when the user closes his/her browser. Persistent cookies are used to make tasks like logging into the Site easier for returning users by remembering a user’s login information. Persistent cookies stay on a user’s hard drive from one session to the next. Cookies may be used for many purposes, including, without limitation, remembering you and your preferences and tracking your visits to our web pages. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a persistent or session cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off such cookies through your browser settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you choose to disable cookies on your device, some features of the Site may not function properly.

**Web Beacons/GIFS.** Small graphic images or other web programming code called web beacons (also known as “1×1 GIFs” or “clear GIFs”) may be included in our web pages and messages. Web beacons may be invisible to you, but any electronic image or other web programming code inserted into a web page or e-mail can act as a web beacon. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including, without limitation, to count visitors to our Site, to monitor how users navigate the Site, to count how many e-mails that were sent were actually opened or to count how many particular articles or links were actually viewed.

**Embedded Scripts.** An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the Site such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your device used to access Site from our web server or a third party service provider, is active only while you are connected to the Site, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.

**e-tags/cache browsers/web logs.** Like most standard website servers, we log IP addresses (a unique number assigned to every computer on the Internet) and device identification in order to improve security, analyze trends and administer the Site. We may track your movement within the Site, the pages from which you were referred, access times and browser types. This information may include the browser you are using, the Internet address from which you linked to our Site, the operating system of your computer, the unique IP address of the computer or device identification from the mobile device that you used to access our Site and usage and browsing habits. We use this information in the aggregate to gauge the effectiveness, usage, and popularity of our Site, track information for statistical purposes, help diagnose and troubleshoot server malfunctions, analyze trends, track user movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information. We may also use individual information we collect through web logs to send you targeted offers and other communications.
